It is an elegant and type-safe object-oriented language that enables
developers to build a variety of secure and robust applications
that run on the .NET Framework. You can use C# to create traditional
Windows client applications, XML Web services, distributed components,
client-server applications, database applications, and much, much more.
.NetFramework
C# programs run on the .NET Framework, an integral component of Windows
that includes a virtual execution system called the common language
runtime (CLR) and a unified set of class libraries. The CLR is the
commercial implementation by Microsoft of the common language
infrastructure (CLI), an international standard that is the basis
for creating execution and development environments in which
languages and libraries work together seamlessly.
In addition to the run time services, the .NET Framework also includes an
extensive library of over 4000 classes organized into namespaces that
provide a wide variety of useful functionality for everything from file
input and output to string manipulation to XML parsing, to Windows Forms
controls. The typical C# application uses the .NET Framework class library
extensively to handle common plumbing chores.