Developer Tools
Presentation layer technologies - RadControls, the industry’s leading UI component
suites for ASP.NET AJAX, Silverlight, Windows Phone 7, WPF and Windows Forms and
the Telerik Extensions for ASP.NET MVC
Productivity tools – The essential tools for code analysis, refactoring ,mocking,
decompiling, and memory and performance profiling
Reporting engine – Telerik Reporting, the easiest way to create embedded and printable
reports for all .Net platforms.
Data Access – OpenAccess, a convenient tool for building powerful data layers for all
popular databases through a visual designer
Kendo UI - everything you need to build sites and mobile apps with JavaScript and HTML5

Agile Project Management
TeamPulse – the tool that helps teams organize their work, collaborate, share knowledge
and ultimately deliver results every time. Agile or not, TeamPulse will help your
software team get things done.

Automated Testing Tools
Test Studio - the industry’s premier tool for automated testing of 
WPF, ASP.NET AJAX and MVC applications

Web Content Management
Sitefinity – the next-generation web platform for public websites and intranets
trusted by over 8,000 customers.