Telerik’s mission is to make software development easier and more enjoyable.
Hello World!
allow companies of all sizes to create richer, more stable and aesthetic software 
faster than ever before. Trusted by over 100,000 customers worldwide for our 
Hello World!
professionals maximize their productivity and "deliver more than expected” every day.
As true craftsmen, we don't believe in compromises and our goal is to only 
release tools that we can be proud of.
Hello World!

Developer Tools
Presentation layer technologies - RadControls, the industry’s leading UI component
Hello World!
Hello World!
Productivity tools – The essential tools for code analysis, refactoring ,mocking,
Hello World!
Reporting engine – Telerik Reporting, the easiest way to create embedded and printable
reports for all .Net platforms.
Data Access – OpenAccess, a convenient tool for building powerful data layers for all
popular databases through a visual designer
Hello World!
Hello World!
Agile Project Management
TeamPulse – the tool that helps teams organize their work, collaborate, share knowledge
Hello World!
Hello World!
Hello World!
Automated Testing Tools
Test Studio - the industry’s premier tool for automated testing of 
WPF, ASP.NET AJAX and MVC applications

Web Content Management
Sitefinity – the next-generation web platform for public websites and intranets
Hello World!
